Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Alumni Association Records, 1895-2012 UA.6.5.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Events, 1986-2007; VI.
  - Basketball, 4.
    - Big East Tournament, March 8-11, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Basketball Season, 2006-2007 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Football, 5.
    - Football Games- ARAMARK Sauer Box (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - NCAA Football Violations (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Liberty Bowl, December 31, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 16-19)
    - Bowl Game To-Do List, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Home Game Tailgate Tent, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Football Kick-off Luncheon, September 4, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Football Kick-off Luncheon, September 2, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Pitt Stadium Celebration, November 12-13, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Football Kick-off Luncheon, September 1, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Friday Night Live, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Game Day Information, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 27-28)
    - Pitt at Temple, November 18, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Football Season, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Game Day Information, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Pitt at Notre Dame, October 6, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 32-33)
    - Tangerine Bowl, December 20, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 34-35)
    - Football Tickets, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Football Kick-off Luncheon, August 30, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Pitt at Notre Dame, October 12, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Pitt at Miami, November 21, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Insight Bowl, December 26, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Pregame Tent, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Football Season, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Football Kick-off Luncheon, September 5, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Pitt vs. Kent State, September 6, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Pitt vs. Ball State, September 13, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Pitt at Toledo, September 20, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Pitt at Texas A&M, September 27, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Pitt vs. Notre Dame, October 11, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Pitt at Rutgers, October 18, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Pitt vs. Syracuse, October 25, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Pitt at Boston College, November 1, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Pitt vs. Virginia Tech, November 8, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Pitt at Temple, November 22, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Pitt vs. Miami, November 29, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Continental Tire Bowl, December 27, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Pitt at South Florida, September 6, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Pitt at Temple, October 9, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Pitt at Notre Dame, November 13, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Fiesta Bowl, January 1, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Football Tickets & Panther Club Donation, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Awards, 6.
    - Awards and Medals- Distinguished Alumni, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 27-28)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 29-30)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 31-32)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 33-34)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award- Honors Convocation, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 37-38)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award- Honors Convocation, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award- Honors Convocation, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award- Yolanda Barco, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award- Frank Bolden, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award- Frances Hesselbein, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award- Allen Roses, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 8-9)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award- Honors Convocation, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award- Herbert Douglas, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award- Thomas Usher, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 15-16)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Distinguished Alumni Fellows Award, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Hall of Honor (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Volunteer of the Year, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Volunteer of the Year, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Volunteer of the Year, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Volunteer of the Year, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Recognition Awards (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Awards- General (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Awards Inventory, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Prominent Alumni & Nominations (Box 34, Folder 27-28)
    - Distinguished Daughters of Pennsylvania Award- Bibiana Boerio, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Alumni Awards at Other Universities (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - University on the Road, 7.
    - University on the Road, 1999-2000 (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
    - University on the Road- Boston, October 14, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 3-4)
    - University on the Road- Philadelphia, March 19, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - University on the Road- Washington, D.C., April 2, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - University on the Road- Philadelphia & Washington, D.C., March 19, 2000/April 2, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - University on the Road- Boca Raton & Naples, Florida, January 24-25, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 8-9)
    - University on the Road- New York City, February 25, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 10-12)
    - University on the Road- San Diego, May 1, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - University on the Road- Los Angeles, May 2, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - University on the Road- San Francisco, May 3, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - University on the Road- California, May 1-3, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - University on the Road- California Follow-up, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - University on the Road, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - University on the Road- Philadelphia & Washington, D.C., April 9-10, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - University on the Road, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - University on the Road- Los Angeles, January 28, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - University on the Road- Ft. Lauderdale, February 18, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - University on the Road- Chicago, November 7, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - University on the Road, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - University on the Road- Summer Discovery Showcase Event, June 23, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 5-7)
    - University on the Road- Stem Cell Presentations, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - University on the Road- Stem Cell Presentation, Boca Raton, FL, March 13, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - University on the Road- Stem Cell Presentation, Washington, D.C., May 3, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - University on the Road- Stem Cell Presentation, Chicago, August 22, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Chancellor's Tour, 8.
    - Chancellor's Tour, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Chancellor's Tour- South Florida, February 6, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Chancellor's Tour- Philadelphia, April 3, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Chancellor's Tour- Washington, D.C., April 15, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Chancellor's Tour- Chicago, May 2, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Chancellor's Tour- Harrisburg, May 21, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Chancellor's Tour- New York City, May 28, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Chancellor's Tour- Erie, June 12, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Pitt Day, 9.
    - Pitt Day in Pittsburgh, August 31, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 20-21)
    - Pitt Day in Harrisburg, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Pitt Day in Harrisburg, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Pitt Day in Harrisburg, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Pitt Day in Harrisburg, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Pitt Day in Harrisburg, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Pitt Day in Harrisburg, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Lecture Series, 10.
    - Signature Series Lectures, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Signature Series Lectures- Evaluations, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Signature Series Lectures, 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Signature Series Lectures- Evaluations, 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Signature Series Lectures, 2004-2005 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Signature Series Lectures, 2005-2006 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Downtown Lecture Series, October 8, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Pittnics, 11.
    - Pittnics, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Pittnics, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Pittnics, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Pittnics, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Pittnics, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Discovery Weekend, 12.
    - Discovery Weekend, October 27-28, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 12-16)
    - Discovery Weekend- Correspondence, October 27-28, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Discovery Weekend- Promotional Material, October 27-28, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Summer Discovery Showcase, 13.
    - Summer Discovery Showcase, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Summer Discovery Showcase- Material, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Summer Discovery Showcase- Plan & Committee, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Summer Discovery Showcase- Meeting Minutes, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Summer Discovery Showcase- Public Affairs & Publications, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Summer Discovery Showcase- Attendance, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Summer Discovery Showcase- MAN Presentation, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Summer Discovery Showcase- Academic Marketplace (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Summer Discovery Showcase- Host Committee, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Summer Discovery Showcase- Budget, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Summer Discovery Showcase- Facilities/Food/Entertainment, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Summer Discovery Showcase- Staff Schedules & Training, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Summer Discovery Showcase- Volunteer Information, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Dinners & Receptions, 14.
    - Heinz Chapel Choir Concert and Dinner, December 5, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Heinz Chapel Choir Concert and Dinner, December 3, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Heinz Chapel Choir Concert and Dinner, December 2, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Summit Dinner Meeting, April 15, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Jesse Owens Dinner, February 11, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Jewish National Fund Tree of Life Dinner, October 16, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Pitt Ambassadors Scholarship Dinner, February 26, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Cathedral of Learning Society Dinner, June 24, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Marshall Goldberg Reception, May 21, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Networking Reception, March 9, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - General Events, 15.
    - Estate Planning Seminar, October 15, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Best of Both Worlds Academic/Athletic Expo, April 23, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Founders Day, February 27, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Tom Ablauf Memorial Golf Tournament, June 21, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 19-20)
    - Commencement, April 29, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Ralph Nader and Pat Buchanan Debate, November 15, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Pitt Start, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Freshman Orientation, August 22-25, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Night of the Panther, August 25, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Presentations, 2002-2003 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - MBNA Alumni Director Summit, April 22-24, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - PAA Orientation Presentation- Eva Blum, May 17, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Theatre, 2003-2004 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Symphony, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Kuntu Theatre, March 28, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Member Orientation, April 6, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - RSVP Lists- Orientation Lunch, Special Guest Lunch, April 23, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - San Francisco Event, June 25-27, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Roger Williams Visit to PAA, August 23, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Chesapeake & Potomac Pitt Club Golf Tournament, September 26, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Pathway to Professions, Oct. 21, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - 66th Senior PGA Championship, May 23-29, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Dean's Council Presentation, September 15, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Legacy Laureate, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Member-Get-A-Member Drive, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Higher Education 50th Anniversary Celebration, March 31, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - PAA School of Nursing Golf Outing, July 21, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Honors Convocations (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - Presentation- Partnerships by Program (Box 38, Folder 45)
- Programs and Projects, 1994-2007; VII.
  This series contains records related to the various programs and projects initiated by the Alumni Association. The main subseries relate to the Banner Program, campaigns, and the plans regarding the conversion of the Masonic Temple into Alumni Hall. There are also records related to the issues surrounding the demolition of Pitt Stadium.
  - Chancellor's Circle, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - License Plate Program, 1995-2001 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Interdisciplinary Projects, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - Masonic Temple Page Marker Project, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - School/College/Campus Alumni Relations Program, 2003-2005 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Legacy Project, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 51-52)
  - Athletics (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - Banner Program, 1.
    - Banner Program, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Banner Program- Packet, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Banner Program- Correspondence, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Banner Breakfast, October 28, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Banner Qualification Forms, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Banner Qualification Forms, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 6-7)
    - Banner Qualification Forms, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
    - Banner Qualification Forms, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Campaigns, 2.
    - National Alumni Campaign, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 11-13)
    - Capital Campaign, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Endowment Campaign Plan, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Endowment Campaign, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 16-17)
    - Advocacy Campaigns, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Stadium Issue, 3.
    - Stadium Issue, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 19-24)
    - Stadium Issue, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Ad Hoc Stadium Resolution Committee, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Building Plans, 4.
    - Hillel Center, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Jewish University Center, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Connolly Ballroom, 2006-2007 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Masonic Temple/Alumni Hall
      - Masonic Temple Adaptive Reuse Proposal, June 4, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Masonic Temple/Alumni Hall Blueprints, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Redesign of Alumni Association Offices, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 8-10)
      - Alumni Center Project, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 11-12)
      - Survey of Alumni Centers (Box 40, Folder 13-16)
      - Alumni Center Committee Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 17-20)
      - Alumni Center Feasibility Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 21-23)
      - Alumni Center Open House, April 8, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Alumni Center Open House, April 8, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Alumni Center Dedication, June 9, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 2-3)
      - Other Alumni Centers/Halls of Fame, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
- Professional Organizations, 1999-2006; VIII.
  This series contains records of the several professional organizations of which the Alumni Association is a member. Former Executive Director Lee Patouillet was an active member of these groups, so these records reflect primarily his participation and interests.
  - Council of Alumni Association Executives (CAAE), 1.
    - CAAE General Communications (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - CAAE Historical Member Lists (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - CAAE Email Survey, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 8-12)
    - CAAE Surveys, 2000-2003 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - CAAE Summer Institute, July 28 - August 1, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - CAAE Summer Institute- John Clemens, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - CAAE Summer Institute- Frances Hesselbein, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - CAAE Summer Institute- Lake Lawn Resort, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - CAAE Winter Institute, February 15-17, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - CAAE, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - CAAE Alumni Roster, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - CAAE Board Meetings, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - CAAE Correspondence- Alumni Roster, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - CAAE Correspondence- Special Needs Alumni, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - CAAE Winter Institute, February 14-16, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - CAAE Summer Institute, July 27-30, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - CAAE, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - CAAE Correspondence- Alumni Hall of Fame, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - CAAE Correspondence- Alumni Registration, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - CAAE Correspondence- 15th Year Reunion, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - CAAE Winter Institute, February 20-22, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - CAAE Summer Institute, July 24-27, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - CAAE Credit & Solicitation, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - CAAE Internet Advising Survey, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Council for Advancement and Support of Education (CASE), 2.
    - CASE Circle of Excellence Program (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - CASE/AIR Conference Presentation, April 23-24, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - CASE Research Journal, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - CASE Research in Advancement Summit, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - CASE District 2 Conference, January 29 - February 1, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - CASE Annual Assembly, July 15-17, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - CASE 5 Conference, December, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - CASE District 2 Conference, February 5-7, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - CASE Summit for Advancement Leaders, July 8-11, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - CASE Summit for Advancement Leaders- Correspondence, July 8-11, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement- Planning, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement- Planning, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement- Planning, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement- Correspondence, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement- Planning, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement, February, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement, June, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement, November, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement, March, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement, June, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement, October, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement, March, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement, June, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - CASE International Journal of Educational Advancement, October, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - CASE Handbook of Institutional Advancement, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 35)
- Publications, 1925-2012; IX.
  This series contains copies of the various publications produced by the Alumni Association. Included is the early Alumni Review, the published annual report of the organization, the Pitt Advocate Newsletter, the Alumni Connections Newsletter, and other miscellaneous publications.
  - Alumni Review, 1.
    - Alumni Review, May/June, October, November 1936 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Review, January-June 1937 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Review, 1943-1944 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Alumni News Review, April 1950 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Alumni Review, October 1962 & April, July 1963 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Association Annual Report, 2.
    - Alumni Association Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Association Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Association Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Association Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Association Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Association Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Association Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Association Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Association Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Association Annual Report, 2002-2003 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Pitt Advocate Newsletter, 3.
    - Pitt Advocate Newsletter, January, February, April, September, December 2000 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Pitt Advocate Newsletter, April, June, August, December 2001 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Pitt Advocate Newsletter, March, July, September, December 2002 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Pitt Advocate Newsletter, April, July 2003 & January 2004 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Connections Newsletter, 4.
    - National Alumni Association Leaders Newsletter, Spring 1991 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Spring, Fall 1994 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Winter, Spring, Summer, Fall 1995 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Winter, Spring, Fall 1996 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Summer, Fall 1997 & Summer, Fall 1998 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Spring, Summer, Fall 1999 & Spring, Summer 2000 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Winter, Summer, Fall 2001 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, June, Fall 2002 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Winter, Summer, Fall 2003 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Spring, Summer, Fall 2004 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Spring, Summer, Fall 2005 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Spring, Fall 2006 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Winter, Spring, Summer 2007 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Spring, Summer 2008 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Al umni Connections Newsletter, Spring, Summer 2009 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Spring, Summer 2010 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Alumni Connections Newsletter, Spring, Summer 2011 & Spring 2012 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Other Publications, 5.
    - The Pitt Panther, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - The Alumni Times, Autumn 1982 (Box 43, Folder 38)
- Early History, 1895-1952; X.
  This series contains some of the earlist records of the Alumni Association. Most of the records are from the late nineteenth and early twentieth centuries, with the newest material dating to 1952.
  - Graduating Class Grades (undated) (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Minutes from a Meeting About Football (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Pitt Victory Song Lyrics and Sheet Music (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Pitt Panther Cartoon (copy) (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Second Alumni Yearbook, 1895 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - News Article- Pitt Junior College Notes, c. 1891-1911 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - General Alumni Association Letter Regarding Alumni Banquet, 1899 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Pittsburgh Postcard and Matchbook, 1911 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - University of Pittsburgh Commencement Program, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Report of the Meetings of the Association of Alumni Funds, 1925-1926 (Box 43, Folder 48)